http://www.preventingviolence.org.nz/privacy-policy

0508 744 633
hide my visitI need helpfree HelplineLive Web ChatWhat is domestic abuse?i am afraid of my partneri am experiencing violencei am being stalkedi am using violenceI have been strangled or chokedWomen's RefugeSafe Use of TechnologySafety PlanningWorkplace Safety Planningprotection orderspolice safety ordershelp someone you knowi want to helpDonate NowFinancial HelpDonating ItemsVolunteer for ShineFundraiseBusiness HelpDonation Tax Rebateshelp someone you knowBe a Conversation Champion
how shine helpsShine ServicesHelplineShine Advocateswomen's refugekidshineno excusestrainingDVFREE™ WorkplaceCustomer ResponseShine in SchooltestimonialsNews, events & trainingLatest Newsin the mediaEventsTrainingDVFREE™ Workplacevacanciessee it allDVFREE™ WorkplaceDonate NowLight It OrangeCorporate PartnersShopTraining & EventsDVFREE WorkplaceResourcesResource RoomShine Reports and Articlestraining & seminarsshine service resourcesintro to domestic abuseGender and domestic abuseNZ Law & Domestic AbuseMyths and FactsWhy negotiating is unsafeDay of a Shine AdvocateStephen's StoryVacanciesAbout Usthe shine storyvision mission & valuesour peopleOur FundersShine HistoryContact
SHINE OFFICE:
(09) 815 4601
OFFICE HOURS:
MON - FRI 8:30 - 4:30PM
PRIVACY POLICY
TERMS OF TRADE
SHIPPING INFO
© 2015 SHINE
DESIGN BY HUSK
(0)
LOG OUT
donate now
Quick exit
Shopping cart is empty.
donate now
Quick exit
Privacy Policy
Shine is committed to protecting your privacy.
We will only use the data which we collect about you lawfully in accordance with the Privacy Act 1993.
Personal information gathered by Shine is kept in confidence. Only Shine personnel and representatives are authorised to access personal information based only on their need to deal with the information for the reason(s) for which it was obtained.
We do not disclose any personal information obtained about you to third parties. Shine does not rent, sell or trade our mailing lists.
We provide our donors with an opportunity to remain anonymous and to request that their name and/or the amount of their gift not be publicly released.
When you use any of the Shine Facebook apps, such as the safe@home app, Shine does not request access to your profile. We will only have access to information you supply by entering into the application. Shine also allow you to share elements of the Application. Your engagement with Shine through the Shine-administered Facebook page or any other Shine social media account is governed by the existing privacy rules and policies of those social media platforms.
If at any time you wish to receive less mail, email or wish to stop receiving any of our communications, simply contact us by phone at 09 815 4597 or via e-mail at enquiries@2shine.org.nz.
If you have any concerns, suggestions or complaints related to this policy please direct them to the Communications and Development Director at the same email address.
Shine takes credit card security seriously. We use a Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard compliant hosted payment service, Direct Payment Solutions (DPS), to process the credit card transactions. We do not collect or store your credit card details. Your credit card payment details will only be collected and held securely by DPS.
Click to read our Donor Privacy Policy document
Share
Tweet
© SHINE Ltd
0508 744 633
enquiries@2shine.org.nz
PO Box 90279, Victoria Street West, Auckland 1142
Design by HUSK
Shopping cart is empty.
Click here to chat with us
